UNITE Posters 6000 G
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Posters
1997-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workers United
6000 G
2.22 cubic feet
2.2 linear ft.
Graphic arts.
7514200
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 14, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6284 G: Workers United Poster
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Textile Workers Union of America; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization); Workers United
7514200
- UNITE! - sign (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  blue nylon material over a wooden frame [9x27 in.]
- Federated May Not Care - But We Do! - sign (Box 1, Folder 2)
  gray metal [18.5x22.5 in.]
- UNITE!, Make this a Holiday Season of Conscience Shop Sweat Free (Box 1, Folder 3)
  poster [18x21.5 in.]
- UNITE!, Fighting for our jobs (Box 1, Folder 4)
- UNITE!, Victory at Kmart (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UNIDAD!, Elecciones 1996, Luchando por nuestras Familias (Box 1, Folder 6)
- UNIDAD!, !A detener el expreso! (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE!, Taking control of our time (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UNITE! And / y !UNIDAD!, Telling our story, Presentando nuestra historia (Box 1, Folder 9)
  poster [18x21.5]
- Sheet of UNITE! Clothing labels (framed) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  cloth [18x21.5]
- UNITE - Harassment & Discrimination (Box 1, Folder 11)
  6 Broadsides
- UNITE -- Sweatshop, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Fast Track Express - Graphic (1997)
- unite -- Block Prints -- Richard Wock(?) [1998] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  5 Prints
- Union Health Center, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  1 Broadside
- UNITE - Posters & Broadsides (Box 1, Folder 15)
  8 designs
- UNITE -- Health & Safety (Box 2, Folder 1)
- UNITE -- Organization & Demonstration (Box 2, Folder 2)
  13 Broadsides
- UNITE -- Graphics (Box 2, Folder 3)
  1 Graphic
- UNITE -- Color Illustrations -- Cliff Worth (Box 2, Folder 4)
  10 color sketches/illustrations
- Lollan Schoenstein Graphics (Box 2, Folder 5)
  37 color and black and white graphics
- Clothing labels (Box 2, Folder 6)
  5 label examples / graphics
- UNITE Cover Art (Box 2, Folder 7)
  4 graphics
- UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Fast Rrack (NAFTAS); UNITE! Founding Convention June 29-30, 1995 (Box 3)
  - UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Fast Track (NAFTAS) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    1 poster, 8 broadsides
- UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Brand Names (Box 4)
  - UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Brand Names (Box 4, Folder 1)
    8 Broadsides, 4 Posters
- UNITE -- Calendars (1995-2003) (Box 5)
  - UNITE -- Calendars (1995-2003) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UNITE -- Voting, Registration, Candidate Support (Box 6)
  - UNITE -- Voting, Registration, Candidate Support (Box 6, Folder 1)
    1 Poster, 1 sheet of Graphics
- UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Postal Uniforms (Box 7)
  - UNITE -- Sweatshops -- Postal Uniforms (Box 7, Folder 1)
    4 Poster boards